homesandland.com 2018-08-15

# Homes & Land Privacy Policy | Homes & Land ®

You can browse HomesAndLand.com without revealing personal information about yourself. Like nearly all web sites, we monitor and log the incoming "IP Addresses" of visitors. This anonymous information is collected to assist us in analyzing site use patterns and to help us maintain a secure environment for our site's data. This information is not shared with any other party. 

Certain features of our web site request that you enter personal information, including your name, address, email address, phone number, etc. These features include, but are not limited to requests for a free magazine, emails sent to advertisers, and emails sent to Homes & Land Publishers. You are under no obligation at any time to provide us with personal information, although some features may function incompletely or improperly without it. Any feature that requests personal information from you will include a link to this Privacy Policy. 

HomesAndLand.com is a venue designed to promote the magazines of NewPoint Franchisor, LLC and to assist consumers in contacting its advertisers. Therefore, some of the information you send us is shared with our Publishers and their advertisers. Neither Homes & Land Publishers nor their advertisers are governed by this privacy policy. 

Some Advertisers on HomesAndLand.com provide links to other web sites not controlled by HomesAndLand.com. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. 

HomesAndLand.com may share aggregate information with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. For example, we may disclose what searches visitors to HomesAndLand.com perform most often. 

By using the HomesAndLand.com web site and providing your personal information, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy. NewPoint Franchisor, LLC may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

We use Google Anaytics data to collect non-personally identifiable information such as age, gender and interests in order to customize offerings to best suit our site visitors. 

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions or concerns you may have. Our email address is [privacy@homesandland.com](mailto:privacy@homesandland.com).
